Finding Aid for the Allegra Fuller Snyder papers, 1960-2010 LSC.1881
UCLA Library Special Collections
- UCLA Administrative Papers., 1960-2010
  - Management in the Arts., 1971-1974 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Participant list for colloquium "Politics of the Arts." Internships program and list. Graduate School of Management MA in Management in the Arts brochure. May 1972 newsletter.
  - Museum of Cultural History-Faculty Advisory Committee., 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Draft of "Project Planning Guide for Museum of Cultural History Building." Budget. UCLA procedures for "Acquisition and Disposal of Works of Art, Antiquities, and Artifacts." Newsclippings. Meeting agendas and notes. Sept. 1975 draft "Master Plan: Museum of Cultural History."
  - New York Residence Fellowship Program Committee., 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Correspondence including Pia Gilbert. Six finalists were UCLA students.
  - Provost Review Committee., 1982-1987 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Five-year review of Provost Raymond L. Orbach. Faculty reviews. Committee meeting notes, correspondence, recommendations.
  - Pueblo, People and Performances., 1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    NEH application for "Pueblo, People and Performances: the role of dance in Los Angeles history."
  - Royce Two-Seventy., 1979 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Orientation meeting agenda, correspondence.
  - School of the Arts-Faculty Chair., 1988-1991 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    1989-1990 Annual Report. Correspondence reviewing Department of Design. Search for Dean School of the Arts including correspondence with Franklin D. Murphy, Chair of search committee.
  - Student Contacts., 1988 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Printout of faculty and students associated with the Dance Department.
  - Tape Logs., 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Dictating machine tape logs for letters from AFS.
  - Undergraduate Admissions., 1979-1981 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    University of California admissions application brochures and packets.
  - Undergraduate Affairs-Executive Advisory Committee (1 of 2)., 1976-1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Meeting agenda, minutes. Funding proposals, budgets. Course proposal. Instructional Improvement Plan questionnaire results. Oct. 1976 "Proposal for Educational Programming Funds in the UCLA Residence Halls." June 1976 "UCLA Undergraduate Instructional Improvement Plan."
  - Undergraduate Affairs-Executive Advisory Committee (2 of 2)., 1976-1978 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Meeting agenda, minutes. Funding proposals, budgets. "UCLA Teaching Assistant Training Program."
  - Undergraduate Education-Special Committee on Cultural Diversity (1 of 2)., 1977-1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Draft of Committee on Cultural Diversity May 1979 report. Letter from American Indian Studies Center. Statistical summary of attrition by ethnic and economic categories. Meeting minutes. Nov. 1977 "The Academic Advancement Program: ITS evolution, current status, and future directions.
  - Undergraduate Education-Special Committee on Cultural Diversity (2 of 2)., 1979 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    "Chicano Studies Center Recommendation on Chicano Student Recruitment, Admissions and Retention." Meeting agenda, minutes. Long-range enrollment planning task force. Preparation packet for undergraduates by Relations with Schools Program.
  - Undergraduate Student Support, Honors, Prizes., 1988-1991 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Meeting agendas. President's fellowship rating order. Regents Scholars. May 1990 meeting of the Legislative Assembly. Fall 1988 "Person to Person: Undergraduate admissions and relations with schools." Draft of "Regents Scholar Society: Constitution."
  - UCLA Research Grants., 1984-1989 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    AFS research funding applications for 1989 Dance Ethnology and Choreocinema; 1987 "Gestures in Context" materials for Osaka, Japan conference; 1986 compilation of dance ethnology writings; and 1984 sabbatical field notes for lecture.
  - University of California, San Diego., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Dance Day letter from Yen Lu Wong regarding AFS keynote speech.
  - Visual Communications Studies., 1972 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    "Visual and Communication Studies at UCLA: A trial balloon."
  - World Arts and Cultures (WAC)-1985-1986. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Reader for Winter 1986 WAC 190A, Senior Colloquium. 1985-1986 Annual Report. Brochure. Faculty meeting minutes, correspondence. Academic Senate's external reviewer's report. Newsletters. See also Box 43 Ethnic Arts.
  - World Arts and Cultures-1986-1987. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Dance Ethnology projected two-year cycle. Newsletters. Sept. 1986 Committee on Undergraduate Courses and Curricula report on WAC program. Correspondence. Rosters of WAC students.
  - World Arts and Cultures-1987-1988. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    1987-1988 WAC Student handbook. Rosters of WAC students. Newsletter. Meeting minutes, correspondence. WAC art course proposal.
  - World Arts and Cultures-1988-1989. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    "Asian Roots of the Music and Dance Traditions of Los Angeles Area Asian Immigrants" course proposal. 1988-1989 WAC Student handbook. Rosters of WAC students. Global Vision Newsletters. Meeting minutes, correspondence. Changes in Music concentration proposal.
  - World Arts and Cultures-1989-1990. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Rosters of WAC students. Meeting minutes, correspondence. Proposed concentration changes. Global Vision Newsletters.
  - World Arts and Cultures-1990-1991. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Admissions and course requirements and statistics. Meeting minutes. 1990-1991 WAC Student handbook. Global Vision Newsletters.
  - World Arts and Cultures-2005. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Letters regarding the history and future of WAC.
- Performance Programs., 1940-2010
  This is a collection of published programs from performances that AFS attended. The performances were sponsored by the Dance and Ethnic Arts Departments, other UCLA departments, UCLA Committee on Fine Arts, Greater Los Angeles venues, nationwide venues, and international venues. Most of the ephemera are programs, but there are some flyers and posters. The listings are only selected and not comprehensive.
  - Art Programs., 1962-1997 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Art books and programs for exhibits and collections that AFS attended including "Stravinsky and the Dance."
  - Museum and Structure Programs., 1950s-1996 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Books and brochures for sites including the United Nations, Old Mission Santa Ines, Will Rogers State Historic Park, Southwest Museum Handbook, Descanso Gardens, and Hearst Castle.
  - Performance Programs-Undated (1 of 3). (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Flyers and programs to performances including "Wild Strawberries," "The Committee," "Collages," "Diff'rent," "Annunciation," "Hiroshima… Mon Amour," "James Joyce's Women," "The Quare Fellow," the Bolshoi Ballet, Theatre Vanguard, UCI dance department, UCLA departmental performances. Performances by Kate Hughes and Fanchon Bennett, Martha Kalman, Jhaveri Sisters Manipuri Dance Group, and the Morcas.
  - Performance Programs-Undated (2 of 3). (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Flyers and programs to performances including puppet theater, "L'Avventura," "Life and Death Above a Bowling Alley," "The Knack… and how to get it," Lynn Dally in "Riffs." Tickets to premier of "The Big Country." "The World of Buckminster Fuller" by Robert Snyder. The 4th and 5th "Music and Dance on the Grass and other UCLA departmental performances.
  - Performance Programs-Undated (3 of 3). (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Flyers and programs to performances including "The Ten Company Festival," "Lust for Life," "The Servant of Two Masters," Harkness Ballet, "Bayanihan," and other UCLA departmental performances.
  - Performance Programs-1940s., 1949 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    New York City Dance Theatre at New York City Center. "All the King's Men" at Adams Memorial Theatre, Williams College.
  - Performance Programs-1951. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    New York City Dance Theatre at New York City Center. "Angel in the Pawnshop," "Transformation: Arts, communication, environment." Gian-Carlo Menotti's "The Medium."
  - Performance Programs-1952. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Martha Graham at Julliard. New York City Dance Theatre at New York City Center. "Caesar and Cleopatra" and "Antony and Cleopatra" at Ziegfeld Theatre with Vivien Leigh. "Of Thee I Sing." "Venus Observed" with Rex Harrison. Inaugural program at the Beekman "Never Take No For an Answer." "Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival."
  - Performance Programs-1953. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    "New Faces of 1952." "Porgy and Bess" and "The New Dance Group"at the Ziegfeld Theatre. "American Dance" choreographed by Graham, Limon, Cunningham, Lang, McGehee, Fonaroff, Humphrey, and O'Donnell. The Town Hall of New York programs. New York City Dance Theatre at New York City Center. Bennington College Dance Group at Julliard. "Hollywood Ice Revue."
  - Performance Programs-1954. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    The Town Hall of New York programs. New York City Dance Theatre at New York City Center. New York City Opera. "Ondine" with Audrey Hepburn and Mel Ferrer. "Tea and Sympathy" produced by Elia Kazan. Stadium Concerts, College of the City of New York.
  - Performance Programs-1955. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Budapest String Quartet at Carnegie. Vicente Escudero. "The Saint of Bleecker Street." Jennie Tourel.
  - Performance Programs-1956. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    The American Mime Theatre. The San Francisco Opera. The Playgoer programs. "The Lark." "The Chalk Garden." The Yugoslav National Folk Ballet.
  - Performance Programs-1957. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    "Colombe" and "Waiting for Godot" at Dahl Theatre. San Francisco Opera at the Shrine. "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof" at Huntington Hartford. Marian Seldes in "Witness for the Prosecution." Ojai Festival. "The Bewitched-A dance satire" by Nikolais and Louis. Los Angeles Music Festival. Pacific Coast Figure Skating Championships."
  - Performance Programs-1958 (1 of 2). (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Playbills for "West Side Story," "The Family Reunion," "The American Ballet Theatre," "The New York City Ballet." Hollywood Bowl Program for second week. "Beryozka Russian Dance Company."
  - Performance Programs-1958 (2 of 2). (Box 51, Folder 1)
    La Jolla Playhouse programs. "The Matchmaker" with Mabel Albertson. "Giselle" with Alicia Alonso and Igor Youskevitch. Autographed Carnegie program by Jennie Tourel. "James Joyce's Ulysses in Nighttown." American National Theatre and Academy Children's Theatre Festival at El Capitan. New York City Ballet booklet with photos by George Platt Lynes.
  - Performance Programs-1959. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    "Breathless." UCLA Spring Festival of Music. Playbills for New York City Ballet and "La Plume de Ma Tante." The Bolshoi Ballet at the Shrine. "A Game of Gods" at UCLA. New York City Ballet booklets. 31st Annual Academy Awards Presentation program, presentation tickets, Governor's Ball tickets and invitation.
  - Performance Programs-1960 (1 of 2). (Box 51, Folder 3)
    "Ballet Africains." "The Threepenny Opera." Jai Alai games in Tijuana. Georgian State Dance Company. Marcel Marceau. Carlos Montoya.
  - Performance Programs-1960 (2 of 2). (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Playbills for Martha Graham, New York City Ballet, "Dear Liar." Programs for The Theatre Group / University Extension at UCLA. Book and program for Royal Danish Ballet. Inbal Dance Theatre of Israel.
  - Performance Programs-1961 (1 of 2). (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Leningrad Kirov Ballet at the Shrine. Screening of "A Visit with Pablo Casals" by Robert Snyder. Programs of UCLA Committee on Fine Arts Productions. Programs of The Theatre Group University Extension, UCLA. Pacific Coast Figure Skating Championships.
  - Performance Programs-1961 (2 of 2). (Box 51, Folder 6)
    33rd Annual Academy Awards membership screenings schedule. Tournament of Roses. Eugene Loring's Dance Players. Program and booklet for Moiseyev Dance Company.
  - Performance Programs-1962 (1 of 2). (Box 52, Folder 1)
    American Ballet Theatre, UCLA Theatre Group and Committee on Fine Arts, New York City Ballet, "How To Succeed in Business Without Really Trying," "Sunday in New York," "Child Buyer."
  - Performance Programs-1962 (2 of 2). (Box 52, Folder 2)
    34th Annual Academy Awards documentary films screenings schedule. Programs for "Mutiny on the Bounty" by MGM, New York City Ballet, Glen Tetley dance, Julliard dance, Marcel Marceau, Christmas From Many Lands, Seattle World's Fair Science exhibit. Booklet for "Lawrence of Arabia." Robert Joffrey Ballet. "Go Ice Capades." American Ballet Theatre.
  - Performance Programs-1963 (1 of 2). (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Playgoers for The Theatre Group's "Spoon River Anthology," "Brecht on Brecht," "A Summer of Repertory." The Royal Ballet. Playgoers for Wilshire-Ebell productions. UCLA Committee on Fine Arts programs for Feb., March, July, and Sept./Oct.
  - Performance Programs-1963 (2 of 2). (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Synanon Foundation production. Fourth, ninth, and eighth Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra Symphonies for Youth. Programs and booklet for "An Evening with the Royal Ballet." American National Theatre and Academy Children's Theatre Festival. Booklet for Ukrainian Dance Company.
  - Performance Programs-1964 (1 of 2). (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Playgoers for The Theatre Group's "The Seagull," "P.S. 193." "Lindy Opera House." UCLA Committee on Fine Arts programs for Feb. 1-15, Feb. 17-29, March, April, Sept. 26-Oct. 4, and Nov.
  - Performance Programs-1964 (2 of 2). (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Feb. 21 and 22 "Bayanihan Philippine Dance Co." at Pasadena Civic Auditorium. 36th Annual Academy Awards Short Subjects Nominations. Julliard programs of Draper/Humphrey/Limon/Sokolow and Tudor ballet. New York Philharmonic and "Fialka" at Lincoln Center. "Finngymnasts and Their Native Land." Poster for "Sanctum" by Nikolais. Booklet for The Royal Ballet.
  - Performance Programs-1965 (1 of 3). (Box 53, Folder 2)
    14th California State College Long Beach art film festival. Playgoers for The Theatre Group's "Robert Frost / Promises to Keep" and "Yeats." UCLA Committee on Fine Arts programs for Feb., April, June-July, Dec. 2-12 and Spring Film Series.
  - Performance Programs-1965 (2 of 3). (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Los Angeles Music Festival and "The Mother of Us All" at UCLA. American Ballet Theatre at the Greek Theatre. "History of Movement: A danced lecture by Angiola Sartorio."
  - Performance Programs-1965 (3 of 3). (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Los Angeles Philharmonic Symphonies for Youth with Zubin Mehta. New York City Ballet at Lincoln Center. UCLA Dance Department performance flyers and programs. Program and booklet for The Royal Ballet. Marian Seldes performs in "Medea" at Valley Music Theatre. Booklet for "Mazowsze: Polish song and dance company."
  - Performance Programs-1966 (1 of 2). (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Lang's "Prayer to the Dark Bird." LA County Fair. City Center Joffrey Ballet. UCLA Concerts programs for March 19-April 2, Martha Graham, and Spring Film Series. Bunraku at the Wilshire-Ebell. See Box 63, folder 1 for oversized booklet.
  - Performance Programs-1966 (2 of 2). (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Los Angeles County Museum of Art "Five Choreographers in Three Dance Concerts" with Trisha Brown, Alex Hay, Robert Rauschenberg, Claes Oldenburg. "Talking Pictures" UCLA student films. Booklets for City Center Joffrey Ballet, American Ballet Theatre, the film of the Royal Ballet Romeo and Juliet, Bolshoi Ballet, Moiseyev Dance Company. Toho La Brea Theatre productions "Kill" and "Kuroneko." UCLA Dance Department productions. See Box 63, folder 2 for oversized booklet of Murray Louis.
  - Performance Programs-1967 (1 of 3). (Box 54, Folder 2)
    National Dance Guild's "Second Concert of Contemporary Dance." "Imago" Nikolais Dance Company and Murray Louis. Music Guild Season. UCLA Dance faculty lecture series. UCLA programs for Carmen de Lavallade, Jose Greco, Anna Sokolow Dance Company. Playbill for "Before You Go" with Marian Seldes.
  - Performance Programs-1967 (2 of 3). (Box 54, Folder 3)
    LA Philharmonic with Zubin Mehta. UCLA programs for "Sybil Shearer, Dancer," "Mass Remembered: A choreographic oratorio," "Kinetic Contrasts," and "Parables and Poems." "Directors Guild of America Annual Awards Dinner."
  - Performance Programs-1967 (3 of 3). (Box 54, Folder 4)
    "The Happy Time" at the Ahmanson. Booklets for The Royal Ballet, Martha Graham Dance Company, Ballet Folklorico, and Bayanihan Philippine Dance Company.
  - Performance Programs-1968 (1 of 3). (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Performing Arts at UCLA programs for Jan. Ravi Shankar, March Marcel Marceau, and Nov. 1-16 Merce Cunningham. Bayanihan at the Greek Theatre. Playbill and booklet for Netherlands Dance Theater. June Wilshire-Ebell program.
  - Performance Programs-1968 (2 of 3). (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Performing Arts at UCLA program for Oct. Danzas Venezuela. Synanon's "This Day is the First Day of the Rest of Your Life." "Agee" with Marian Seldes.
  - Performance Programs-1968 (3 of 3). (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Booklets for the film "Isadora," American Ballet Theatre. Programs for Royal Shakespeare Company, and "Up With People," American Ballet Theatre.
  - Performance Programs-1969 (1 of 3). (Box 55, Folder 3)
    UCLA programs for "Yugoslav Dance and Music Traditions," "Les Indes Galantes," "Delusion of the Fury." 41st Annual Academy Awards screenings schedule. Bella Lewitzky Dance Company. July 15-19 Hollywood Bowl. "Theater 1969 Dance Repertory." New York City Ballet.
  - Performance Programs-1969 (2 of 3). (Box 55, Folder 4)
    UCLA program for Jose Limon. Oct. 1-7 "The Grand Kabuki." See also Box 63, folder 3 for related oversized booklet. Director's Guild of American Annual Awards Dinner. "Easy Rider" promotional flyer. "Letters of a Javanese Princess" with Marian Seldes. Los Angeles Festival of the Performing Arts "A Ceremony of Us." "UCLA Extraordinary Jubilee."
  - Performance Programs-1969 (3 of 3). (Box 55, Folder 5)
    "Man of La Mancha" by Los Angeles Civic Light Opera. "The Adventures of the Black Girl in her Search for God." The Julliard School "Dedication Concert." Booklets for The Stuttgart Ballet and The National Ballet. Flyer for "Long Beach Summer School of Dance."
  - Performance Programs-1970 (1 of 3). (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Flyer for Claes Oldenburg's "Sort of a Commercial for an Icebag." Brochure of films "Africa-As Seen by Africans." "Hair" at the Aquarius Theater. Martha Graham Dance Company at the Brooklyn Academy of Music. UCLA programs for Feb. 22 - March 8, March 12-18, and Dec.
  - Performance Programs-1970 (2 of 3). (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Programs for "The Dream on Monkey Mountain," City Center Joffrey Ballet, "Idiot's Delight." "Festival of the Performing Arts" program and brochure listing AFS and Buckminster Fuller as members of the Festival Committee.
  - Performance Programs-1970 (3 of 3). (Box 56, Folder 3)
    42nd Annual Academy Awards screenings schedule. "Iranian Dance, Ballet and Music." Elle Johnson Dance Company. "No More Mondays" produced for the White House Conference on Children. "The First Evening." The Los Angeles Dance Theatre. Booklets for Marcel Marceau and Ballet West.
  - Performance Programs-1971. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    The Performing Arts at UCLA programs for Jan. 21-Feb. 6, Feb. 7 - March 7, and March 14-April 16. Flyer for "Inner City Repertory Dance Company." Long Beach School of Dance University Dance Company. UCLA Dance Department student concerts. Valentina Oumansky Dramatic Dance Ensemble. Program and booklet for Pasadena Pacific Regional Ballet Festival.
  - Performance Programs-1972 (1 of 3). (Box 56, Folder 5)
    "The Whirling Dervishes of Turkey." UCLA programs for "Chinese Shadow Puppets," "Phantom India," "Ah Ahk," "The Jose Limon Dance Company," "James Cunningham & the Acme Dance Company." The Performing Arts at UCLA programs for Jan. 28-Feb. 6, Feb. 12-March 12, and May 12-26.
  - Performance Programs-1972 (2 of 3). (Box 56, Folder 6)
    UCLA Dance Company. "The Fifteenth Presentation of Films Produced by the Students of the Motion Picture-Television Division, Department of Theater Arts, UCLA." Cal Arts student dance concerts. International Ballet School-West "The Group." "Yugoslav Performance Group." UCLA Dance Department student concerts. Hollywood Bowl 50th Birthday Superseason. "Don't Bother Me, I Can't Cope."
  - Performance Programs-1972 (3 of 3). (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Program and booklet for Antonio Gades and his Spanish Dance Company. Booklets for the Spoleto Festival in Italy June 21-July 9, New York City Ballet, The Pennsylvania Ballet.
  - Performance Programs-1973 (1 of 2). (Box 57, Folder 2)
    UCLA Dance Department, Art Council and Senior concerts. New York City Ballet at the Greek Theatre. Teatro Internacional. Ingmar Bergman's "Cries and Whispers." Theatre Vanguard's "Margalit" and "I am I-An evening with Gertrude Stein." Connecticut College 26th American Dance Festival.
  - Performance Programs-1973 (2 of 2). (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Royal Shakespeare Company in "A Midsummer Night's Dream." Dancers and Musicians of Bali. Program and booklet for American Ballet Theatre.
  - Performance Programs-1974. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    UCLA Dance Company, Lighting Showcase, Martha Graham, Dance/LA, Thesis concerts, Contemporary Music Festival. "The Bacchae of Euripides." American Ballet Theatre. The Pennsylvania Ballet. "Music from Iran." The National Dance Company of Senegal. Los Angeles Dance Currents "Rug Concerts." Los Angeles Ballet Theatre. Pilobolus Dance Theatre at Inner City Cultural Center. "Savages." National Shadow Theatre of Malaysia.
  - Performance Programs-1975. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    UCLA Dance Company, Senior concerts, Thesis concerts, Pilobolus Dance Theatre, "Chhau, the Masked Dance of Bengal," "Aman," "Indrani," "Danzas y Musica de Mexico," Burmese National Theater. "Yaqui Indian Deer Dance" performed by LaGuardia High School of Music and Arts, New York. Bella Lewitzky Dance Company. "Equus." Erick Hawkins Dance Company.
  - Performance Programs-1976. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    UCLA Dance Company, Lighting Showcase, Thesis concerts, "Indrani," "The Ik," "Ballet Nacional de Festivales de España," "Mummenschanz," Polish Mime Theater, Marilyn Horne. Invitation and program to the Thai Association of Southern California's "King's Ball" to celebrate His Majesty's birthday.
  - Performance Programs-1977. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    UCLA Dance Company, Lighting Showcase, Thesis concert, Senior concerts, "Pongsan Masked Dance-Drama of Korea," "Gamelan and Dance of Indonesia," "An Evening of Asian Dance," "Yamini Krishnamurti." Jules Feiffer's "Hold Me!" "Eyes Wide Open Dance Theatre." Artists in Prison, Inc. Sheldon Film Theater. Booklets for Ballet San Marcos and Ballet West.
  - Performance Programs-1978 (1 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Performing Arts at UCLA "Bugaku" and The Martha Graham Dance Company. American Dance Festival. College at Purchase Dance Theatre Lab. 3rd Annual Disco Dance Championships of Los Angeles. "Hello Dolly." "Deathtrap." "Runaways." Paul Taylor Dance Company.
  - Performance Programs-1978 (2 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 3)
    "Bharata Natyam" by Medha Yodh. Jose Limon Dance Company with Erik Bruhn at the Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine. 2nd Los Angeles Dance Festival. "Eurythmeum Stuttgart." "One" by John Marshall and Arielle Thomas. "Zoot Suit." Program and booklet for Martha Graham Dance Company at UCLA.
  - Performance Programs-1979 (1 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 4)
    UCLA Dance Company, Senior concerts, "Indrani and Sukanya," "African Humanities Institute," "Kei Takei's Moving Earth," Music and Dance of Bali, Gamelan and Dance from the Court Tradition of Central Java, "Bharata Natyam and Kathakali," "Sendra Tari from Sunda," Asian Performing Arts Festival, Jose Limon Dance Company, Pilobolus Dance Theatre. "Aman." "Dance / LA."
  - Performance Programs-1979 (2 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 5)